funny-base.com 2013-05-23

# FUNNY BASE - Privacy Policy.

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR FUNNY-BASE.COM**  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate funny-base.com commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Any personal information that you provide to funny-base.com shall stay absolutely safe, private and secure. We **DO NOT** share or resell personal information to outside sources.

 **INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED**  
Funny-base.com **DO NOT** log any information about you, your computer, your internet service provider or your internet connection.

 **COOKIES**  
Funny-base.com **DO NOT** use cookies to store information about your visits. However, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, Google advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

 **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**  
Funny-base.com works with Google AdSense and Fastclick that serve ads to this site. Google AdWords may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information please see the [Google Privacy Policy Statement](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

 **EXTERNAL LINKS**  
Funny-base.com contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **CONTACTING OUR WEB SITE**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can contact us.
